<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <DesignatorCapturePawn>Capture downed pawn</DesignatorCapturePawn>
  <DesignatorCapturePawnDesc>Capture chosen pawn to make him a prisoner. Your colonists assigned to this work will automatically bring pawn to prisoners bed. Works same as right clicking to capture.</DesignatorCapturePawnDesc>
  <MessageMustDesignateDownedForeignPawn>Pawns must be downed and not be of your faction.</MessageMustDesignateDownedForeignPawn>
    <DesignatorCapturePawn_CE>Do CE Stabilize and Capture downed pawn</DesignatorCapturePawn_CE>
  <DesignatorCapturePawnDesc_CE>Capture chosen pawn to make him a prisoner. Your colonists assigned to this work will try Stabilize(CE) them and automatically bring pawn to prisoners bed. Works same as right clicking to capture.</DesignatorCapturePawnDesc_CE>
    <DesignatorCapturePawn_FirstAid>Do FirstAid and Capture downed pawn</DesignatorCapturePawn_FirstAid>
  <DesignatorCapturePawnDesc_FirstAid>Capture chosen pawn to make him a prisoner. Your colonists assigned to this work will try do FirstAid([RH2]BCD:First Aid) and automatically bring pawn to prisoners bed. Works same as right clicking to capture.</DesignatorCapturePawnDesc_FirstAid>
  <SmarterCaptureThem>Smarter Capture Them</SmarterCaptureThem>
  <bleedoutMinHoursSetting>Rescue Pawn with hours to bleed out more than:</bleedoutMinHoursSetting>
  <giveUpMissingOrganSetting>Give up pawn missing vital organ</giveUpMissingOrganSetting>
  <giveUpMissingOrganSettingDesc>Death Rattle allow Pawn to remain alive (for a while) with vital organ missing. Do not capture these pawn.</giveUpMissingOrganSettingDesc>
  <maxBleedoutFirstAid>Max bleedout hour to perform first aid</maxBleedoutFirstAid>
  <checkForDangerSetting>Check for danger when capturing</checkForDangerSetting>
  <checkForDangerSettingDesc>By dafault, pawn will not perform rescue if there is danger around target. This may cause delay in rescue. Disable at your own risk</checkForDangerSettingDesc>
  <doVanillaTendSetting>Do vanilla tending before capture</doVanillaTendSetting>
  <doVanillaTendSettingDesc>Pawn will try to tend target using vanilla tending. Note that a pawn will very low medical skill may take too long tend.</doVanillaTendSettingDesc>
  <doArrestFirstSetting>Arrest target first</doArrestFirstSetting>
  <doArrestFirstSettingDesc>Make sure target don't stand up and fight your doctor by arresting them with the arrest here provided by [RH2] CPERS: Arrest Here!</doArrestFirstSettingDesc>
</LanguageData>